

### CONTACT

1

+32491632234

 $\searrow$ 

matiwouters@gmail.com

mathiaswouters.com

Oud-Turnhout, Belgium



LinkedIn



<u>Twitter</u>

# MATHIAS WOUTERS

## CLOUD & CYBER SECURITY STUDENT

#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Mathias Wouters, and I'm 21 years old. Currently, I'm studying Cloud and Cyber Security. I am social, friendly, stressresistant, responsible, and ambitious. In my free time, I like to read books and keep myself busy with new technologies.

#### **EDUCATION**

Thomas More, Geel | 2021 - now Bachelor Cloud & Cyber Security

HT20, Turnhout | 2019 - 2021 **Electromechanics** 

Sint-Pietersinstituut, Turnhout | 2014 - 2019

Mathematics & Sciences

#### **EXPERIENCES**

Job student | 2017 - 2023

#### Colruyt

- Help customers
- Fill shelves
- Working at the cash register

Job student | 2023 - now

#### **Get Driven**

75%

80%

70%

- Professional customer interaction
- Providing chauffeur services
- Responsible handling of customers/vehicles

#### **HOBBIES**

Scout leader

Traveling

Reading books

#### **SKILLS**

Linux 85
Cloud (AWS - Azure) 75

Kubernetes & Docker

Cisco Networking

Windows

Python

#### LANGUAGES

Dutch - Mother tongue

English - C1

French - B1

German - A1